After three months of job searching,
The job boards gave to me:
1200 Phantom Job postings
11 “We found someone better”s
1,000 AI Rejection Letters
9 Rescheduled Meetings
800 Indeed submissions
700 ZipRecruiter positions
60 Disappearing recruiters
50 Cover letters
4 Custom résumés
3 Timed coding projects
2 Seventh-round rejections
And a desperate LinkedIn plea.
50 Cover letters
4 Custom résumés
3 Timed coding projects
2 Seventh-round rejections
And a desperate LinkedIn plea
It seems so hard.
It might get better.
Or much, much worse.
1200 Phantom Jobs
11 “We found someone better”s
1,000 AI Rejection Letters
9 Rescheduled Meetings
800 Indeed submissions
700 ZipRecruiter positions
60 Disappearing recruiters
50 Cover letters
4 Custom résumés
3 Unpaid coding projects
2 Seventh-round rejections
And a desperate LinkedIn plea
It seems so hard.
It might get better.
Or much, much worse.
All thanks to ChatGPT :-(